A Aisha Amate

+63 966 400 9309 <u>alhime1225@gmail.com</u>

**Quezon City** 

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A fullstack developer with expertise in MERN Stack and design, as well as overseeing all facets of Software Development Life Cycle, from analysis and design to implementation and maintenance. My interest in software development started when it was introduced to me in high school after which it turned into a growing passion, learning new technology and exploring the field of IT has been really fulfilling and enjoyable.

### **WORK HISTORY**

May 2020 - May 2022

#### Individual Trader and Fund Manager, MFF

- Market Analysis (Technical and Fundamental)
- · Identifying patterns
- · Stock forecasting

May 2018 - May 2020

#### Consultant, QA Consulting

- Using Maven projects and test suite using Junit
- Using selenium and cucumber alongside Junit, using various concepts such as; data driven testing (DDT), test driven development (TDD) and behavioural driven development (BDD)
- DDT concept is used with selenium to automatedly test websites, BDD was used to create user stories using Cucumber

September 2018 - September 2019

#### QA Engineer, NETBuilder

- Involves reviewing Business requirements, IT Design documents and preparing Test Plans which involve various Test Cases for all assigned modules/projects
- Created Test plan & Script, Defect Management Templates; Created Initial test plan and developed test cases and test scripts manually
- Developed a Defects Tracking Log for the SharePoint Site to track defects while testing
- Involved in UAT testing, SIT Testing, Regression Testing and Functional testing
- Prepared & published Daily & Weekly QA status reports
- Actively participated in all QA and testing activities during Dev, FT, UAT and PROD SDLC (Software Development lifecycle)
- · Having hands on experience in device testing mobile and tablet device testing
- Involved in cross browsing testing (compatibility testing) of the application on various browsers to ensure it functions

 Having hands on experience in component testing, integration testing and regression testing

## **PROJECTS**

### Simple Portfolio:

https://aisha-folio.netlify.app/

### Simple JS Game:

https://js-game-aisha.netlify.app/

# **EDUCATION**

Current

Uplift Code Camp, MERN Stack

June 2018

**Bachelor of Science**, Computing With Games Development **University of Greenwich**, Old Royal Naval College, Park Row, London SE10 9LS

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Level 2 Creating a Business Start-Up, 2022 Level 2 Customer Service in NCFE, 2022 BCS Certificate in ISTQB Foundations, 2018 Oracle Leadership 2016